sun-001	8	Tutorials	Tutorials
mon-keynote	1	Keynote	Keynote: John H. L. Hansen
mon-002	6	Oral	Model of Speech Perception
mon-003	6	Oral	Speaker Verification: Advances in Speaker Embeddings
mon-004	6	Oral	Spatial Audio 1
mon-005	6	Oral	Scaling and Zero-Shot Speech Synthesis
mon-006	6	Oral	Multi-Talker ASR & Speaker Diarization
mon-007	6	Oral	Search Methods and Inference Algorithms
mon-008	6	Oral	Multimodal Spoken Dialogue Systems
mon-009	6	Long Oral	Speech Representations and Alignment
mon-010	6	Long Oral	Robust and Efficient ASR
mon-011	11	Poster	Tools and Techniques for Phonetic Analysis
mon-012	8	Poster	Paralinguistics
mon-013	10	Poster	Spoofing and Deepfake Detection 1
mon-014	14	Poster	Evaluation of Speech and Audio Analysis
mon-015	12	Poster	Generative and Self-Supervised Speech Enhancement
mon-016	9	Poster	Long-Form Speech Synthesis
mon-017	7	Poster	Information Extraction and Retrieval
mon-018	8	Poster	Clinically Useful Speech Representations 1
mon-019	12	Challenge	Audio Reasoning Challenge
mon-020	6	Oral	Tones
mon-021	5	Oral	Speech Emotion Recognition and Representation 1
mon-022	6	Oral	Speech Deepfake Detection: Robustness, Generalization, Attribution
mon-023	6	Oral	Audio segmentation
mon-024	5	Oral	Neural Speech Enhancement: Survey, Diffusion and Flow Matching
mon-025	6	Oral	Audio-Visual Grounding, Synchronization & Video Understanding
mon-026	6	Oral	Spoken Language Processing: Evaluation and Metrics
mon-027	6	Oral	Assistive Technologies 1
mon-028	6	Long Oral	Text-to-Speech Synthesis
mon-029	10	Poster	Brain Studies and Speech
mon-030	11	Poster	Audio Understanding and Representation Learning
mon-031	9	Poster	Neural Speech Codecs: Low-Bitrate and Disentangled Coding
mon-032	11	Poster	From Self-Supervised Pre-training to Phonetic Analysis of Speech Models
mon-033	10	Poster	Reasoning with Speech/Audio Language Models
mon-034	9	Special Session	Methods and data for vocal tract and articulation analysis
mon-035	13	Poster	Grand Special Challenges Poster Showcase
mon-036	8	Show And Tell	Speech Synthesis, Voice Conversion and Audio Generation
tue-037	6	Oral	Voice Quality Aspects of Speech
tue-038	6	Oral	Speaker Verification and Anti-Spoofing
tue-039	6	Oral	Acoustic Event Detection 1
tue-040	6	Oral	Language-Model and Codec-Token Speech Enhancement
tue-041	6	Oral	Controllable and Expressive Speech Synthesis
tue-042	6	Oral	Resource Constrained Speech Recognition
tue-043	6	Oral	Datasets
tue-044	6	Oral	Multimodal and Non-Speech Healthcare Applications
tue-045	6	Long - Oral	Multilingual Speech 1
tue-046	5	Long Oral	Pronunciation Diversity
tue-047	11	Poster	Speech Emotion Recognition and Representation 2
tue-048	11	Poster	Audio signal analysis
tue-049	9	Poster	Target Speaker Extraction, Speech Separation and Audio Understanding
tue-050	9	Poster	Singing Voice and Music Generation
tue-051	11	Poster	Multilingual, Cross-lingual & Low-Resource ASR
tue-052	7	Poster	Prosody, Pronunciation and Specialized Speech Processing
tue-053	9	Poster	Speech and Language Technologies in Healthcare
tue-054	10	Special Session	Pacific Voices: Speech Science and Technology for the Languages of the Pacific Ocean
tue-055	1	Keynote speaker	Prof Steven Bird
tue-056	6	Oral	Modeling L1 Acquisition
tue-057	6	Oral	Multilingual and Cross-Lingual Paralinguistic Analysis and Processing
tue-058	6	Oral	Language and Dialect Recognition
tue-059	6	Oral	Spatial Audio 2
tue-060	5	Oral	Low-Resource Speech Synthesis
tue-061	6	Oral	Speech Synthesis Evaluation 1
tue-062	5	Oral	Audio Language Models
tue-063	5	Oral	Clinically Useful Speech Representations 2
tue-064	6	Long Oral	Audio Coding and Signal Analysis
tue-065	7	Poster	Perception and Appraisal of Prosody
tue-066	11	Poster	Spoofing and Deepfake Detection 2
tue-067	11	Poster	Acoustic Event Detection 2
tue-068	9	Poster	Quality, Intelligibility and Evaluation of Speech and Codecs
tue-069	10	Poster	Text Processing for Speech Synthesis
tue-070	9	Poster	Cross-Lingual and Multilingual Speech Recognition 1
tue-071	8	Poster	Pathological Speech Assessment 1
tue-072	5	Special Session	Safeguarding Synthetic Speech: Ethical, technical and legal perspectives
tue-073	7	Special Session	Indigenous Voices in Speech Science and Technology
tue-074	9	Show And Tell	Speech and Language Learning Technologies
tue-075	6	Oral	Prominence, Stress and Focus
tue-076	6	Oral	Source Separation 1
tue-077	6	Oral	Real-Time, Low-Latency and Edge Speech Enhancement
tue-078	6	Oral	Multilingual & Low-Resource ASR
tue-079	5	Oral	Low-Resource & Endangered Language Speech Processing
tue-080	5	Oral	Empathetic Dialogue and Interaction Dynamics
tue-081	6	Oral	Audio & Speech Language Models: Evaluation, Representations, and Emerging Capabilities
tue-082	6	Oral	Corpus Creation, Summerisation and Understanding
tue-083	6	Long Oral	Spoofing, Deepfake Detection and Watermarking
tue-084	5	Long Oral	Audio-Visual and Multimodal Perception
tue-085	10	Poster	Speech Production and Perception 1
tue-086	8	Poster	Cross-Linguistic and L2 Phonetic Studies
tue-087	10	Poster	Spatial Audio 3
tue-088	11	Poster	Instruction-following and Controllable Speech Synthesis
tue-089	10	Poster	Robust ASR: Uncertainty and Confidence
tue-090	12	Poster	Speech Technologies for Language Learning & Assessment
tue-091	8	Poster	Spoken Dialogue Systems
tue-092	7	Poster	Pathological Speech Assessment 2
tue-093	8	Special Session	Queer and Trans Speech Science and Technology
wed-094	6	Oral	Multimodal Emotion Recognition
wed-095	6	Oral	Speaker Verification: Architectures, Losses, and LLMs
wed-096	6	Oral	Evaluation, Benchmarking, and Reliability of Audio Systems
wed-097	6	Oral	Neural Audio Codec Architectures
wed-098	6	Oral	Speech Synthesis: Speech Features, Codec and Representations
wed-099	6	Oral	Self-supervised Speech Representation Learning
wed-100	6	Oral	Entrainment and Dialogue Coordination
wed-101	6	Oral	Speech and Language Technologies for Health Applications 1
wed-102	5	Long Oral	Generative Audio and Music
wed-103	6	Long Oral	Clinical and Inclusive Speech Technology
wed-104	7	Poster	Phonetic Aspects of TTS and ASR Systems
wed-105	9	Poster	Speaker Diarization 1
wed-106	9	Poster	Acoustic Event Detection 3
wed-107	8	Poster	Dereverberation, Bandwidth Extension and Restoration
wed-108	11	Poster	Emotional Speech Synthesis
wed-109	10	Poster	Efficient Inference for ASR and Speech LMs
wed-110	10	Poster	Audio Language Models: Reasoning, Reliability, and Multimodal Understanding
wed-111	14	Special Session	Challenges in Speech Data Collection, Curation, and Annotation
wed-112	8	Show And Tell	Speech and Language Processing for Health and Accessibility
wed-113	1	Keynote speaker	Prof Jen Hay
wed-114	1		Lunchtime Panel
wed-115	6	Oral	Neurophysiology of Speech
wed-116	6	Oral	Speaker Diarization 2
wed-117	6	Oral	Audio Foundation Models and Generation
wed-118	6	Oral	Voice Editing
wed-119	6	Oral	Domain Adaptation & Accented ASR
wed-120	6	Oral	Multi-Speaker Processing, Personalization, and Adaptation
wed-121	6	Oral	Robust and Real-World ASR Systems
wed-122	6	Oral	Speech, Voice and Language Disorders
wed-123	6	Oral	Speech and Language Technologies for Health Applications 2
wed-124	6	Long Oral	Speech Enhancement and Restoration
wed-125	8	Poster	Speaker-Specific, Forensic and Segmental Characteristics of Typical and Atypical Speech
wed-126	11	Poster	Behavioral, Cross-lingual, and Multimodal Speech Analysis
wed-127	12	Poster	Speaker Privacy Preservation and Anonymization
wed-128	10	Poster	Active Noise and Echo Control, Sound Zones and Packet-Loss Concealment
wed-129	9	Poster	Streaming Speech Synthesis
wed-130	13	Poster	Multilingual Speech 2
wed-131	10	Poster	Assistive Technologies 2
wed-132	13	Special Session	Speech Science and Computational Modeling to Study Children and their Everyday Environments | CHILDSPACE -- Child Home Interaction & Language Dynamics: Speech, Psychology, Affect, Computation, and Environments
wed-133	5	Oral	Diphthongs and Monophthongs
wed-134	6	Oral	Speaker Identity, States, and Traits in Paralinguistics
wed-135	6	Oral	Speech Deepfake Detection, Attribution and Characterization
wed-136	6	Oral	Speech and Audio Quality Assessment
wed-137	6	Oral	Audio-Visual and Generative Target Speaker Extraction
wed-138	6	Oral	Speech Synthesis Evaluation 2
wed-139	6	Oral	Translation
wed-140	6	Oral	Child Speech and Health
wed-141	6	Oral	Medical Dialogue and Conversational Understanding
wed-142	6	Long Oral	LLMs and Conversational Interaction
wed-143	9	Poster	Speech and Language Representation
wed-144	7	Poster	Acoustic Signal Analysis and Generation
wed-145	10	Poster	Articulatory, EMG, and Visual Speech Generation
wed-146	9	Poster	Robust ASR: Hallucinations and Biases
wed-147	6	Poster	New Architecture and Analyses for ASR and Speech LMs
wed-148	12	Poster	Spoken Language Understanding
wed-149	8	Poster	Pathological Speech Assessment 3
wed-150	16	Special Session	Explainability for Compliance and Trust in Speech AI
wed-151	6	Show And Tell	Speech Analysis, Data Resources and Research Tools
thu-152	5	Oral	Modeling Articulation
thu-153	6	Oral	Speaker Privacy and Anonymization
thu-154	5	Oral	Speech signal analysis
thu-155	6	Oral	LLM Based Speech Synthesis
thu-156	6	Oral	New Training Methods for ASR
thu-157	6	Oral	Code-Switching ASR
thu-158	5	Oral	Information Extraction and Retrieval / Survey Talk
thu-159	6	Oral	Beyond Speech Technologies in Healthcare
thu-160	5	Long Oral	Speaker Diarization and Recognition
thu-161	5	Long Oral	Emotion, Prosody, and Articulation
thu-162	12	Poster	Speaker Recognition and Verification
thu-163	11	Poster	Spatial Audio 4
thu-164	9	Poster	Multi-Channel Processing and Specialized Acquisition (UAV, Radar, Hearables)
thu-165	12	Poster	Speech Synthesis Evaluation and Benchmarking
thu-166	10	Poster	ASR Under Real-World Constraints: Streaming, Adaptation, and Efficiency
thu-167	7	Poster	Multimodal Speech Processing and Speech LLM Systems
thu-168	8	Poster	Speech Benchmarks, Evaluation, and Resources
thu-169	13	Special Session	Post-Training of Speech Foundation Models
thu-170	4	Show And Tell	Speech Recognition, Enhancement and Real-Time Systems
thu-171	1	Keynote speaker	Prof Junichi Yamagishi
thu-172	6	Oral	Gender- and Age-Related Speech Characteristics
thu-173	6	Oral	Audio Watermarking and Source Verification
thu-174	6	Oral	Acoustic Event Detection 4
thu-175	6	Oral	Multi-Channel, Beamforming and Spatial Speech Enhancement
thu-176	6	Oral	Flow Matching for Speech Synthesis
thu-177	6	Oral	Long-form Audio & New Attention Approaches
thu-178	5	Oral	Robust Audio-Visual Speech Recognition
thu-179	6	Oral	Turn-taking
thu-180	6	Oral	Pathological Speech Assessment 4
thu-181	6	Long Oral	Benchmarking Foundation Models
thu-182	9	Poster	Speech Production and Perception 2
thu-183	9	Poster	Speech Emotion Recognition and Representation 3
thu-184	10	Poster	Spoofing and Deepfake Detection 3
thu-185	8	Poster	Source Separation 2
thu-186	10	Poster	SE Architectures, Adaptation and Audio Front-Ends
thu-187	9	Poster	Voice Conversion
thu-188	10	Poster	Cross-Lingual and Multilingual Speech Recognition 2
thu-189	8	Challenge	TidyVoice2026 Challenge: Cross-Lingual Speaker Verification
fri-190	2	Satellite Events	Satellite Events
sat-191	4	Satellite Events	Satellite Events
